export default {
  id: 'jp_word_ms_noun_1_2_1',
  name: '일어달 명사 LV1-2 (100자 / 뜻)',
  data: [
    { question: '危険', answer: ['きけん', '위험'] },
    { question: '季節', answer: ['きせつ', '계절'] },
    { question: '切手', answer: ['きって', '우표'] },
    { question: '切符', answer: ['きっぷ', '표'] },
    { question: '昨日', answer: ['きのう', '어제'] },
    { question: '君', answer: ['きみ', '자네'] },
    { question: '牛丼', answer: ['ぎゅうどん', '소고기 덮밥'] },
    { question: '給料', answer: ['きゅうりょう', '급료'] },
    { question: '今日', answer: ['きょう', '오늘'] },
    { question: '強', answer: ['きょう', '이상 (수량에 우수리 있음)'] },
    { question: '近所', answer: ['きんじょ', '근처'] },
    { question: '空気', answer: ['くうき', '공기'] },
    { question: 'くしゃみ', answer: ['', '재채기'] },
    { question: '薬', answer: ['くすり', '약'] },
    { question: '果物', answer: ['くだもの', '과일'] },
    { question: '口', answer: ['くち', '입'] },
    { question: '首', answer: ['くび', '목'] },
    { question: '雲', answer: ['くも', '구름'] },
    { question: '車', answer: ['くるま', '차'] },
    { question: '怪我', answer: ['けが', '다침, 부상'] },
    { question: '景色', answer: ['けしき', '경치'] },
    { question: '化粧', answer: ['けしょう', '화장'] },
    { question: '喧嘩', answer: ['けんか', '싸움'] },
    { question: '見学', answer: ['けんがく', '견학'] },
    { question: '玄関', answer: ['げんかん', '현관'] },
    { question: '見物', answer: ['けんぶつ', '구경'] },
    { question: '子', answer: ['こ', '자식, 아이'] },
    { question: '公園', answer: ['こうえん', '공원'] },
    { question: '合格', answer: ['ごうかく', '합격'] },
    { question: '交差点', answer: ['こうさてん', '교차점'] },
    { question: '交通', answer: ['こうつう', '교통'] },
    { question: '紅葉', answer: ['こうよう', '단풍이 듦'] },
    { question: 'ゴール', answer: ['', '골'] },
    { question: '心', answer: ['こころ', '마음'] },
    { question: '腰', answer: ['こし', '허리'] },
    { question: '故障', answer: ['こしょう', '고장'] },
    { question: '午前', answer: ['ごぜん', '오전'] },
    { question: '応え', answer: ['こたえ', '반응'] },
    { question: 'ご馳走', answer: ['ごちそう', '진수성찬'] },
    { question: '小包', answer: ['こづつみ', '소포'] },
    { question: '今年', answer: ['ことし', '올해'] },
    { question: '言葉', answer: ['ことば', '언어, 말씨, 단어, 어구'] },
    { question: '子供', answer: ['こども', '아이'] },
    { question: 'この頃', answer: ['このごろ', '요즘'] },
    { question: 'ご飯', answer: ['ごはん', '밥'] },
    { question: 'コピー', answer: ['', '복사'] },
    { question: '先', answer: ['さき', '앞 / 미래 / 전방 / 돌출되어 있는 끝 / 목적지, 상대방'] },
    { question: '作品', answer: ['さくひん', '작품'] },
    { question: '桜', answer: ['さくら', '벚꽃'] },
    { question: '作家', answer: ['さっか', '작가'] },
    { question: '三角', answer: ['さんかく', '삼각'] },
    { question: '試合', answer: ['しあい', '시합'] },
    { question: '仕方', answer: ['しかた', '방법'] },
    { question: '試験', answer: ['しけん', '시험'] },
    { question: '辞書', answer: ['じしょ', '사전'] },
    { question: '次女', answer: ['じじょ', '차녀'] },
    { question: '下', answer: ['した', '아래 / (옷을 안 쪽에 입었을 때) 속, 안'] },
    { question: '舌', answer: ['した', '혀'] },
    { question: '質問', answer: ['しつもん', '질문'] },
    { question: '自分', answer: ['じぶん', '자신, 자기'] },
    { question: '氏名', answer: ['しめい', '이름'] },
    { question: '車道', answer: ['しゃどう', '차도'] },
    { question: '習慣', answer: ['しゅうかん', '습관, 관습'] },
    { question: '習字', answer: ['しゅうじ', '습자, 글자'] },
    { question: '就職', answer: ['しゅうしょく', '취직'] },
    { question: '週末', answer: ['しゅうまつ', '주말'] },
    { question: '修理', answer: ['しゅうり', '수리'] },
    { question: '手術', answer: ['しゅじゅつ', '수술'] },
    { question: '出発', answer: ['しゅっぱつ', '출발'] },
    { question: '趣味', answer: ['しゅみ', '취미'] },
    { question: '準備', answer: ['じゅんび', '준비'] },
    { question: '紹介', answer: ['しょうかい', '소개'] },
    { question: '商業', answer: ['しょうぎょう', '상업'] },
    { question: '昇進', answer: ['しょうしん', '승진'] },
    { question: '招待', answer: ['しょうたい', '초대'] },
    { question: '消防', answer: ['しょうぼう', '소방'] },
    { question: '証明', answer: ['しょうめい', '증명'] },
    { question: '将来', answer: ['しょうらい', '장래'] },
    { question: '食後', answer: ['しょくご', '식후'] },
    { question: '植物', answer: ['しょくぶつ', '식물'] },
    { question: '新型', answer: ['しんがた', '신형'] },
    { question: '信号', answer: ['しんごう', '신호'] },
    { question: '人口', answer: ['じんこう', '인구'] },
    { question: '神社', answer: ['じんじゃ', '신사'] },
    { question: '心配', answer: ['しんぱい', '걱정'] },
    { question: '新聞', answer: ['しんぶん', '신문'] },
    { question: '信用', answer: ['しんよう', '신용'] },
    { question: '寿司', answer: ['すし', '초밥'] },
    { question: '背', answer: ['せ', '키, 등'] },
    { question: '生活', answer: ['せいかつ', '(삶 전체 기준의) 생활'] },
    { question: '精産', answer: ['せいさん', '정산'] },
    { question: '咳', answer: ['せき', '기침'] },
    { question: '責任', answer: ['せきにん', '책임'] },
    { question: '全部', answer: ['ぜんぶ', '전부'] },
    { question: '掃除', answer: ['そうじ', '청소'] },
    { question: '相談', answer: ['そうだん', '상담, 의논'] },
    { question: '袖', answer: ['そで', '소매'] },
    { question: '外', answer: ['そと', '바깥'] },
    { question: '蕎麦', answer: ['そば', '국수, 소바'] },
    { question: '空', answer: ['そら', '하늘'] }
  ]
}
